shaggytexas.com 2016-11-06

# 

## Privacy Policy

Your privacy is critically important to us. At shaggytexas we have a few fundamental principles:

  * We don’t ask you for personal information unless we truly need it. (We can’t stand services that ask you for things like your gender or income level for no apparent reason.)
  * We don’t share your personal information with anyone except to comply with the law, develop our products, or protect our rights.
  * We don’t store personal information on our servers unless required for the on-going operation of one of our services.

### Website Visitors

Like most website operators, shaggytexas collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. shaggytexas’s purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how shaggytexas’s visitors use its website. From time to time, shaggytexas may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.

shaggytexas also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses for logged in users and for users leaving comments on WordPress.com blogs. shaggytexas only discloses logged in user and commenter IP addresses under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information as described below, except that blog commenter IP addresses and email addresses are visible and disclosed to the administrators of the blog where the comment was left.

### Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information

Certain visitors to shaggytexasâ€™s websites choose to interact with shaggytexas in ways that require shaggytexas to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that shaggytexas gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. Those who engage in transactions with shaggytexas are asked to provide additional information, including as necessary the personal and financial information required to process those transactions. In each case, shaggytexas collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitorâ€™s interaction with shaggytexas. shaggytexas does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.

### Aggregated Statistics

shaggytexas may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its websites. shaggytexas may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, shaggytexas does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below.

### Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information

shaggytexas discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on shaggytexasâ€™s behalf or to provide services available at shaggytexasâ€™s websites, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using shaggytexasâ€™s websites, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. shaggytexas will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, shaggytexas discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only in response to a subpoena, court order or other governmental request, or when shaggytexas believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of shaggytexas, third parties or the public at large. If you are a registered user of an shaggytexas website and have supplied your email address, shaggytexas may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with whatâ€™s going on with shaggytexas and our products. We primarily use our various product blogs to communicate this type of information, so we expect to keep this type of email to a minimum. If you send us a request (for example via a support email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. shaggytexas takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.

### Cookies

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitorâ€™s computer, and that the visitorâ€™s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. shaggytexas uses cookies to help shaggytexas identify and track visitors, their usage of shaggytexas website, and their website access preferences. shaggytexas visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using shaggytexasâ€™s websites, with the drawback that certain features of shaggytexasâ€™s websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

### Business Transfers

### Ads

Ads appearing on any of our websites may be delivered to users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by shaggytexas and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

### Comments

### Privacy Policy Changes

Although most changes are likely to be minor, shaggytexas may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in shaggytexasâ€™s sole discretion. shaggytexas encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. If you have a WordPress.com account, you should also check your blogâ€™s dashboard for alerts to these changes. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.
